[{"question":"Which of the following is another name for Software Piracy?","answers":{"a":"Pirates","b":"SOPA","c":"Copyright Infringement of Software","d":"SOSA"},"correct":"c","hint":"It is commonly called this by Government Officials."},{"question":"What is \"torrenting\"?","answers":{"a":"The file type for programs such as Bittorrent to open to obtain illegal files","b":"A file in which it stores your browsing history on your computer.","c":"Visiting a piracy website","d":"Using your computer to remotely take over another computer unwillingly."},"correct":"a","hint":"It has to deal with certain types of files"},{"question":"Which of the following is a Cyberlocker site?","answers":{"a":"PirateBay","b":"RapidShare","c":"Youtube","d":"DailyMotion"},"correct":"b","hint":"A Cyberlocker site is one where you can store many files on a personal account."},{"question":"Which of the following countries has the highest rate of piracy?","answers":{"a":"Armenia","b":"Canada","c":"United States","d":"China"},"correct":"a","hint":"This country's president is named: Serzh Sargsyan"},{"question":"Around the world, many websites are used for piracy, Which of the following is the most used?","answers":{"a":"torrent.com","b":"IsoHunt","c":"TorrentReactor","d":"ThePirateBay"},"correct":"d","hint":"This website is based off of using Torrents."},{"question":"Around the world, Much of the data transfered using P2P networks are copyrighted. Which of the following percentages is the closest?","answers":{"a":"92%","b":"52%","c":"33%","d":"99%"},"correct":"d","hint":"It is significantly high."},{"question":"What is the percentage of softwares that are running worldwide and are downloaded illegally?","answers":{"a":"52%","b":"49%","c":"42%","d":"73%"},"correct":"c","hint":"This number was taken in 2010 and is less than 50%"},{"question":"In 2010, the amount of software downloaded illegally was worth how much?","answers":{"a":"23 Million Dollars","b":"32 Million Dollars","c":"59 Billion Dollars","d":"59 Million Dollars"},"correct":"c","hint":"The software downloaded illegally was worth quite a bit."},{"question":"In 2010, Which of the following movies was pirated the most on the internet?","answers":{"a":"Avatar","b":"Kick-Ass","c":"Inception","d":"Iron Man 2"},"correct":"a","hint":"This movie was also one of the most popular movies in 2010."},{"question":"What is the most pirated piece of software on the Internet?","answers":{"a":"Windows Vista","b":"Windows XP","c":"Microsoft Office","d":"Adobe Photoshop CS"},"correct":"d","hint":"This software is very commonly used for Graphics Design"},{"question":"In 2010, Second most popular movie was Batman: The Dark Knight. How many pirated downloads did it have?","answers":{"a":"10 Million","b":"30 Million","c":"19 Million","d":"17 Million"},"correct":"c","hint":"Avatar, The most popular movie, had around 21 million downloads."},{"question":"In 2010, Many Video Games were pirated for use. Which of the following was the most pirated?","answers":{"a":"Tom Clancy HAWX","b":"Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3","c":"Call of Duty Black Ops","d":"Battlefield 2 Bad Company"},"correct":"d","hint":"This game was created by Treyarch Inc."}]